<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Alexandria Software]]></title>
  <link href="http://blog.alexandriasoftware.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blog.alexandriasoftware.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-10-14T10:23:49-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://blog.alexandriasoftware.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Alexandria Software]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doing Time Version 1.4 Released]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.alexandriasoftware.com/blog/2012/09/10/doing-time-1-dot-4/"/>
    <updated>2012-09-10T05:19:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.alexandriasoftware.com/blog/2012/09/10/doing-time-1-dot-4</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://blog.alexandriasoftware.com/doing-time">Doing Time</a> version 1.4 is now <a href="http://axsw.co/gdZJa6">available on the App Store</a>.</p>

<p>This update includes the following changes:</p>

<ul>
<li><strong>A new application icon.</strong> <img class="right no-border" src="http://blog.alexandriasoftware.com/images/doing-time-app-icon.png"> In this release, I simplified a number of things under the hood, as well as some preferences, and so I made the application icon cleaner to reflect this as well.</li>
<li><strong>Simpler preferences.</strong> <em>Doing Time</em> is a daily counter. I had a complex preference item that allowed the user to set the time (down to five minute increments) that Today would be considered over in <em>Doing Time</em>. I have replaced that with a per-event setting to treat Today as either a completed day or a remaining day in the event being tracked. This also made the date calculations significantly simpler under the hood.</li>
<li><strong>Aggressively redraw events.</strong> <em>Doing Time</em> now takes additional steps to ensure that events are redrawn more frequently, with the added benefit that <em>Doing Time</em> should now be a better-behaving background app and use less memory when another app is in use.</li>
<li><strong>Refactored code.</strong> I rewrote the date calculations mechanism to reduce a lot of complexity, and removed everything that was not being used.</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delays]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.alexandriasoftware.com/blog/2011/12/09/delays/"/>
    <updated>2011-12-09T06:10:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.alexandriasoftware.com/blog/2011/12/09/delays</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I recently returned from a deployment in Afghanistan, and simply readjusting to life back in the United States has been time consuming&#8230;</p>

<p>There&#8217;s also an update to <a href="http://www.axsw.co/doing-time" title="Doing Time">Doing Time</a> in the works with some new features and other internal improvements. I hope to be getting that out in January as well.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
