<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Doing Time | Alexandria Software]]></title>
  <link href="http://blog.alexandriasoftware.com/blog/categories/doing-time/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blog.alexandriasoftware.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-04-26T05:29:23-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://blog.alexandriasoftware.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Alexandria Software]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doing Time Version 1.5]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.alexandriasoftware.com/blog/2013/04/25/doing-time-version-1-dot-5/"/>
    <updated>2013-04-25T07:15:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.alexandriasoftware.com/blog/2013/04/25/doing-time-version-1-dot-5</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="right no-border" src="/images/doing-time-app-icon.png"><a href="/doing-time">Doing Time</a> version 1.4 is now <a href="http://axsw.co/gdZJa6">available on the App Store</a>.</p>

<p>This update includes the following changes:</p>

<ul>
<li><strong>Events by duration.</strong> Doing Time can now create an event knowing either the start date and end date, or the start date and the duration (kind of like how many soldiers get their orders).</li>
<li><strong>OPSEC</strong> It is possible to hide everything but an event's name and the pie chart itself.</li>
<li><strong>Settings per event.</strong> All settings are now per-event, so if you want to hide one event's end date, but not another's, it easy to do.</li>
<li><strong>Count today.</strong> In previous versions of Doing Time, we tried to be smart about handling today, and we failed; now you control it.</li>
<li><strong>Accessibility.</strong> VoiceOver works.</li>
<li><strong>iPhone 5 Ready.</strong> The pie chart is larger on iPhone 5 and the iPod Touch (5th Generation) devices, and the letter boxing is gone.</li>
<li><strong>Bugs squashed.</strong> The calculations for the number of days remaining in an event should be more reliable; other bugs though out the application have been dealt with.</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doing Time Version 1.4 Released]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.alexandriasoftware.com/blog/2012/09/10/doing-time-1-dot-4/"/>
    <updated>2012-09-10T05:19:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.alexandriasoftware.com/blog/2012/09/10/doing-time-1-dot-4</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="/doing-time">Doing Time</a> version 1.4 is now <a href="http://axsw.co/gdZJa6">available on the App Store</a>.</p>

<p>This update includes the following changes:</p>

<ul>
<li><strong>A new application icon.</strong> <img class="right no-border" src="/images/doing-time-app-icon.png"> In this release, I simplified a number of things under the hood, as well as some preferences, and so I made the application icon cleaner to reflect this as well.</li>
<li><strong>Simpler preferences.</strong> <em>Doing Time</em> is a daily counter. I had a complex preference item that allowed the user to set the time (down to five minute increments) that Today would be considered over in <em>Doing Time</em>. I have replaced that with a per-event setting to treat Today as either a completed day or a remaining day in the event being tracked. This also made the date calculations significantly simpler under the hood.</li>
<li><strong>Aggressively redraw events.</strong> <em>Doing Time</em> now takes additional steps to ensure that events are redrawn more frequently, with the added benefit that <em>Doing Time</em> should now be a better-behaving background app and use less memory when another app is in use.</li>
<li><strong>Refactored code.</strong> I rewrote the date calculations mechanism to reduce a lot of complexity, and removed everything that was not being used.</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
